<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<photos>

	<photo>
		<filename>leaves_400x260_01.jpg</filename>
		<title>Target.com</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p align="justify">The earliest anatomically modern human remains found in South Asia are from approximately 30,000 years ago.[13] Nearly  <span class="highlight">India is gr8</span></p>
<p align="justify">By the 5th century BCE, the small chiefdoms of the Ganges Plain and the north-west regions had consolidated into 16 major oligarchies and monarchies called Mahajanapadas.[23][24] T <span class="note">India is gr8</span></p>]]></description>
	</photo>
	
	<photo>
		<filename>leaves_400x260_02.jpg</filename>
		<title>CSK</title>
	<description><![CDATA[<p align="justify">The earliest anatomically modern human remains found in South Asia are from approximately 30,000 years ago.[13] Nearly  <span class="highlight">India is gr8</span></p>
<p align="justify">By the 5th century BCE, the small chiefdoms of the Ganges Plain and the north-west regions had consolidated into 16 major oligarchies and monarchies called Mahajanapadas.[23][24] T <span class="note">India is gr8</span></p>]]></description>
	</photo>
	
	<photo>
		<filename>leaves_400x260_03.jpg</filename>
		<title>Superstar</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<span class="subtitle">Integer pellentesque dignissim diam</span>
<p align="justify">The Indian early medieval age, 600 CE to 1200 CE, is defined by regional kingdoms and cultural diversity.[39] When Harsha of Kannauj, who ruled much of the Ganges plain from 606 to 647 CE, attempted to expand southwards, he was defeated by the Chalukya ruler of the Deccan.[40] When his successor attempted to expand eastwards, he was defeated by the Pala king of Bengal.[40] When the Chalukyas attempted to expand southwards, they were defeated by the Pallavas from farther south, who in turn were opposed by the Pandyas and the Cholas from still farther south.[40] No ruler of this period was able to create an empire and consistently control lands much beyond his core region.[39] During this time, pastoral peoples whose land had been cleared to make way for the growing agriculture economy were accommodated within caste society, as were new non-traditional ruling classes.[41] The caste system consequently began to show regional differences.[41] <span class="highlight">Curabitur euismod scelerisque lacus.</span> Mauris vestibulum felis eget tortor. Praesent mattis varius quam. Vestibulum ullamcorper ipsum nec augue.</p>
<p align="justify">Phasellus ultrices justo non nibh. Sed a eros. <span class="highlight">Phasellus cursus</span> lobortis arcu. Donec scelerisque. Integer ultrices. Cras pretium sem sed odio. Vestibulum nisl mauris, malesuada nec, dictum in, molestie in, pede.</p>]]></description>
	</photo>
	
	<photo>
		<filename>leaves_400x260_04.jpg</filename>
		<title>International</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<span class="subtitle">Quisque ornare pulvinar lorem</span>
<p align="justify">After the 10th century, Muslim Central Asian nomadic clans, using swift-horse cavalry and raising vast armies united by ethnicity and religion, repeatedly overran South Asia's north-western plains, leading eventually to the establishment of the Islamic Delhi Sultanate in 1206.[45] The Sultanate was to control much of North India, and to make many forays i</p>
<p align="justify">Phasellus tempus, justo et laoreet varius, odio mi ultrices libero, nec faucibus dui felis eu dui. Cras ac odio ac mi imperdiet sollicitudin. In hac habitasse platea dictumst.</p>
<p align="justify">Donec hendrerit. Cras ac odio ac mi imperdiet sollicitudin. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. Curabitur euismod scelerisque lacus. Cras pretium sem sed odio. Vestibulum nisl mauris, malesuada nec, dictum in, molestie in, pede.</p>]]></description>
	</photo>
	
	<photo>
		<filename>leaves_400x260_05.jpg</filename>
		<title>Chrysler</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p align="justify" - Sed pretium, neque hendrerit rhoncus accumsan, nibh tellus pharetra neque, quis rutrum elit justo vitae sapien.</p>
<p align="justify">its vast non-Muslim subject population to its own laws and customs.[46][47] By repeatedly repulsing the Mongol raiders in the 13th century, the Sultanate saved India from the devastation visited on West and Central Asia, setting the scene for centuries of migration of fleeing soldiers, learned men, mystics, traders, artists, and artisans from that region into the subcontinent, thereby creating a syncretic Indo-Islamic culture in the north.[48][49] The Sultanate's raiding and weakening of the regional kingdoms of South India paved the way for the indigenous Vijayanagara Empire.[50] Embracing a strong Shaivite tradition and building upon the military technology of the Sultanate, the empire came to control much of peninsular India,[51] and was to influence South Indian society for long afterwards.[50] <span class="highlight">Suspendisse vitae orci a ligula egestas bibendum.</span></p>
<span class="note">Notes: Vestibulum ultrices. Aenean neque. Cras feugiat.</span>]]></description>
	</photo>
	
	<photo>
		<filename>leaves_400x260_06.jpg</filename>
		<title>Vodafone</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<span class="subtitle">Vivamus vulputate felis</span>
<p align="justify">In the early 16th century, northern India, being then under mainly Muslim rulers,[52] fell again to the superior mobility and firepower of a new generation of Central Asian warriors.[53] The resulting Mughal Empire did not stamp out the local societies it came to rule, but rather balanced and pacified them through new administrative practices[54][55] and diverse and inclusive ruling elites,[56] leading to more systematic, centralised, and uniform rule.[57] Eschewing tribal bonds and Islamic identity, </p>
<p align="justify">Proin dui mauris, tempor eget, pulvinar sed, pretium sit amet, dui. Proin vulputate justo et quam. Cras nisl eros, elementum eu, iaculis vitae, viverra ut, ligula. <span class="highlight">Pellentesque metus.</span> Duis dolor.</p>
<p align="justify">Etiam luctus. Quisque facilisis suscipit elit. sollicitudin placerat. Nunc at sem. Sed pellentesque placerat augue. Mauris pede nisl, placerat nec, lobortis vitae, dictum sed, neque.</p>
<span class="note">Notes: Vestibulum ultrices. Pellentesque tempus sapien nec sem commodo ullamcorper. Aenean neque. Cras feugiat. In ut ante.</span>]]></description>
	</photo>
	
	<photo>
		<filename>leaves_400x260_07.jpg</filename>
		<title>Aviva</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<span class="subtitle">Integer pellentesque dignissim diam</span>
<p align="justify">especially under Akbar, the Mughals united their far-flung realms through loyalty, expressed through a Persianised culture, to an emperor who had near divine status.[56] The Mughal state's economic policies, deriving most revenues from agriculture[58] and mandating that taxes be paid in the well-regulated silver currency,[59] caused peasants and artisans to enter larger markets.[57]  </p>
<p align="justify">Proin dui mauris, tempor eget, pulvinar sed, pretium sit amet, dui. Proin vulputate justo et quam. Cras nisl eros, elementum eu, iaculis vitae, viverra ut, ligula. <span class="highlight">Pellentesque metus.</span> Duis dolor.</p>
<p align="justify">Integer ultrices. Donec hendrerit. Cras ac odio ac mi imperdiet sollicitudin. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. <span class="highlight">Curabitur euismod scelerisque lacus.</span> Vestibulum nisl mauris, malesuada nec, dictum in, molestie in, pede.</p>]]></description>
	</photo>
	
	<photo>
		<filename>leaves_400x260_01.jpg</filename>
		<title>Target.com</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<span class="subtitle">Integer pellentesque dignissim diam</span>
<p align="justify">maintained by the empire during much of the 17th century was a factor in India's economic expansion,[57] resulting in greater patronage of painting, literary forms, textiles, and architecture.[60] Newly coherent social groups in northern and western India, such as the Marathas, the Rajputs, and the Sikhs, gained military and governing ambitions during Mughal rule</p>
<span class="note">Notes: Vestibulum ultrices. Pellentesque tempus sapien nec sem commodo ullamcorper. Aenean neque. Cras feugiat. In ut ante.</span>]]></description>
	</photo>
	
	<photo>
		<filename>leaves_400x260_03.jpg</filename>
		<title>Super</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<span class="subtitle">Vivamus vulputate felis</span>
<p align="justify">Fusce quis enim. Aenean eleifend, neque hendrerit elementum sodales, odio erat sagittis quam, sed tempor orci magna vitae tellus. Proin dui mauris, tempor eget, pulvinar sed, pretium sit amet, dui. Proin vulputate justo et quam. Cras nisl eros, elementum eu, iaculis vitae, viverra ut, ligula. <span class="highlight">Pellentesque metus.</span> Duis dolor.</p>
<p align="justify">Vestibulum mauris urna, ultricies vitae blandit non, pellentesque id lectus. Maecenas sem velit, placerat quis ornare in, venenatis sed velit. Aliquam gravida diam ac felis viverra eleifend. Curabitur sed quam tortor, a consequat est. Suspendisse potenti. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.</p>
<p align="justify">Etiam luctus. Quisque facilisis suscipit elit.  sollicitudin placerat. Nunc at sem. Sed pellentesque placerat augue. Mauris pede nisl, placerat nec, lobortis vitae, dictum sed, neque.</p>]]></description>
	</photo>
	
	<photo>
		<filename>leaves_400x260_05.jpg</filename>
		<title>Christ</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<p align="justify">Fusce non lacus et lorem ornare interdum. Nunc eget urna. felis eget tortor. Praesent mattis varius quam. Vestibulum ullamcorper ipsum nec augue. </p>
<p align="justify">Donec hendrerit. Cras ac odio ac mi imperdiet sollicitudin. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. <span class="highlight">Curabitur euismod scelerisque lacus.</span> Cras pretium sem sed odio. Vestibulum nisl mauris, malesuada nec, dictum in, molestie in, pede.</p>]]></description>
	</photo>
	
</photos>